<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ThinkTwor</title>
    <description>Long Form Jekyll theme built with SASS / COMPASS / SUSY</description>
    <link>http://thinktwor.github.io//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://thinktwor.github.io//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 19:42:27 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 19:42:27 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Eyes In the Ocean</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“I had no courage to ask her. I don’t know whether I was afraid or too shy.”, wrote Teasa just after waking up the next day. It was again her dream that was bugging her all over. She wrote the dream just after walking up. In the dream, she was in a classroom with a bunch of friends and it was a history class. The teacher was talking about the Second World War and The Swastik flag. On her way back from school, a friend of her asked her to come over her place for dinner. At home, her mother was also getting ready for a dinner party of a marriage. Coincidentally, they figured out that they both were going the same place for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They went for the dinner together in the evening. It was a marriage reception of a relative. All faces were known. Her mother wanted her to take a picture with the bride and bridegroom. The bride’s eyes caught her attention. It was a Hindu marriage ceremony. The bride looked pretty beautiful and her eyes were down. When she used to take her eyes up, she looked terribly sad. “But thanks to her genius, you couldn’t find her curiously sad look unless you observed her that closely.”, wrote Teasa. Whenever someone came near her, she could immediately put on a smile. The younger brother of the bridegroom helped him grab his suit. After wearing the suit, he looked here and there. He seemed obsessed with something. Perhaps the crowd was the reason behind his worry. Teasa again had a look at the bride. The bride also looked at her. “I saw her eyes speaking something out loud.” she wrote. Her eyes were brown. She seemed thirsty and hungry. Teasa looked up and found that there was no roof. She could see the moon. The moon was incredibly large in size. She could experience a cool breeze and she woke up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As usual, a lot of questions were there in her mind. Later during the day, when she found the yesterday’s newspaper, she saw the pictures of planets taken from NASA. She found it as a  possible explanation for the larger moon in her dream. But what was with that lady? She never had seen a woman like that bride in real life before. The look over her face was quite complex. Her eyes were saying something out loud about her immense sadness of getting married. Perhaps she was just trying to inform Teasa about the crowd, about someone in particular or about the moon. A lot of questions were unanswered. Teasa experienced some unknown faces in the dream. Who knows? They might be the ones with us in different forms, not in coherence with our laws of nature. It is our subconscious which lead us communicate with their real forms in dreams. The bride’s eyes led Teasa swim below the deepest ocean of thoughts and fly over the highest cloud of possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;“I had no courage to ask her. I don’t know whether I was afraid or too shy.”, wrote Teasa just after waking up the next day. It was again her dream that was bugging her all over. She wrote the dream just after walking up. In the dream, she was in a classroom with a bunch of friends and it was a history class. The teacher was talking about the Second World War and The Swastik flag. On her way back from school, a friend of her asked her to come over her place for dinner. At home, her mother was also getting ready for a dinner party of a marriage. Coincidentally, they figured out that they both were going the same place for dinner.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://thinktwor.github.io//eyes-in-the-ocean/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://thinktwor.github.io//eyes-in-the-ocean/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Black White Red Blue</title>
        <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;from-the-original-white-black-red-blue-by-tanuja-pattnaik&quot;&gt;From the original “White Black Red Blue” by Tanuja Pattnaik.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s freezing out here, isn’t it? No, I just don’t get the feeling. What is it then? Feels like I am with my evening suit and having a cup of strong coffee. Oh, where is my coffee? I am now walking with my evening suit. What’s there on my fingers? I can see my face from the water droplet on my fingertip. It’s raining. It’s freezing outside and I get a warm feeling from inside.”, wrote Teasa just after walking up at three in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The perplexities of that dream led her think about the same from time to time. She wrote everything just after waking up. In the dream, it was raining and she eventually had no umbrella with her. It took her sometime to realize that it was really raining. She got to find a place where she could stand a bit. She was thinking of the head girl award of her school just before it started raining. She was thinking of the same even after she found that it was raining. The rain had no effect on her thinking process. She could find a number of people carrying black umbrellas. Then, she suddenly happened to notice her brother carrying a black umbrella and even after watching him she couldn’t ask for any help. She was so obsessed with the head girl award that she couldn’t think of her family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time went on. She was then watching her feet and found mud, which was blood red in color, here and there. She got irritated and thought it was all her mistake of getting out in the evening with no umbrella. She heard a voice calling her name and she could find that was her mother’s voice. She suddenly found her mother near her, and the next moment, her mother was not there. “How could mother vanish without offering an umbrella?”, she asked to herself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she found a book with white cover. The title of the book was “Ghost”. It was not exactly white, but it was like the color of casper, the ghost. When she opened  the book, she found her pictures with her friend Lizzie. Then, she went on reading the contents of that book. It was written “Dedicated to Lizzie”. There was mud all over her feet and she couldn’t realize it until she was able to see a light growing brighter near her face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The light was pretty blue in color and when she found her legs covered with mud, she suddenly screamed and jumped and finally  got herself back on the street. She tried to get rid of the mud with the rain water. She suddenly found her friend Lizzie near her. She was dancing in the rain. Lizzie took her hand and danced with her. She suddenly noticed her brother again with the umbrella and she woke up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As usual, a lot of questions were there in her mind. She finally concluded that her perception towards the scene was changing as time went on like the color of the sky. Black like the midnight sky, red like the evening and morning sky, white like the sky with cloud and blue like the sky with stars.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
          <description>&lt;h4 id=&quot;from-the-original-white-black-red-blue-by-tanuja-pattnaik&quot;&gt;From the original “White Black Red Blue” by Tanuja Pattnaik.&lt;/h4&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://thinktwor.github.io//black-white-red-blue/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://thinktwor.github.io//black-white-red-blue/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Subconscious</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The light, coming from the window glass was so bright that Teasa could hardly notice anything that was written below each portrait at the museum. Teasa was not  interested to go into that museum, but it was compulsory for all the students to attend the visit to the museum and write a report about the same. Teasa saw a lot of things there including shields, swords, crowns, old newspapers and so many other things. It was a tiresome day full of ink, pieces of paper and instructions from the teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On her way back home, she dropped in on her friend to discuss  the homework that they were assigned to complete within that week. Teasa was fond of physics, especially the study of light. People, who were close to her, used to ask their doubts very often related to physics and she was good at discussing things as well.  Helen’s excitement about something was pretty palpable. Her room was not so organized. A large overcoat drooped from her bed. Books were thrown here and there. The floor was full of paints and brushes. “What were you doing?”, asked Teasa. “I was making a sketch of my room.”, replied Helen. After the homework discussion, both of them lolled in their chairs. They were tired. Helen’s mother prepared some food including two cups of hot chocolate for them. Helen remembered a discussion that she had with Teasa a week back. Then, she realized that the discussion was incomplete. All of a sudden Helen asked Teasa about the discussion, which was about the physicist Kaluza Klein. Then, Teasa described the proposal that Kaluza Klein had given years back about the nature of light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teasa returned home at seven in the evening. She had her dinner and went to bed. She started dreaming. In her dream, she saw her maternal grandfather. He was cooking something in the kitchen for her grandmother. The place in that dream was her grandfather’s house. Her grandfather’s voice seemed peculiar.  He came near her, touched her hand and told her to sit down. After sometime, Teasa went into the bedchamber. She saw her grandmother talking to one of her cousins over the telephone. At that very moment, she happened to see that same cousin standing near her and her grandmother was not there. Now Teasa herself was holding the phone and her cousin wanted it back from her. Then, she gave the phone to her cousin, and returned to the kitchen. She saw her grandfather in the dark and noticed that he was sitting alone and doing nothing. It was again her practical thinking about the real life and stimulus which broke her dream and she woke up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again as a connoisseur of dreams, she tried hard to relate that dream to her personal experiences and studies. She found a very good connection between what she had experienced before and the dream. This piece of dream could possibly describe the emotional and hidden aspect of her state of mind. And, her studies led her summarize that her brain worked quickly while dreaming. The fact that her grandfather is dead in real life, broke her dream. The set of physical laws in that dream, according to Teasa, were very unusual and hazy. While writing her dream, Teasa concluded, “The connection of images with shadows is unavoidable and irreplaceable. Really! Light vibrates in the fifth dimension.”&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;The light, coming from the window glass was so bright that Teasa could hardly notice anything that was written below each portrait at the museum. Teasa was not  interested to go into that museum, but it was compulsory for all the students to attend the visit to the museum and write a report about the same. Teasa saw a lot of things there including shields, swords, crowns, old newspapers and so many other things. It was a tiresome day full of ink, pieces of paper and instructions from the teacher.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://thinktwor.github.io//subconscious/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://thinktwor.github.io//subconscious/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Loathsome</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Teasa was getting ready for school. English teacher had given them an assignment, in which each one of them had to collect the history of a poet and present in front of the class. But, before the presentation, the teacher wanted to have a look at the names of the poets that each one of them was to submit to eliminate redundant names. Cris was pretty much confused about the assignment. So, he asked Teasa for suggesting him for a topic. Teasa was also trying to find one for herself. So, she suggested a name to Cris too. Cris was so confused that he asked about the possible sources from where he could get the information about that poet. Teasa helped him to some extent. And, they discussed the history of that poet for some days in school during the lunch break. There was a fear of redundancy among students. If one’s topic of assignment had been taken by any other, one of them had to sacrifice and take another topic. That could be tedious and arduous for one to change the topic for the assignment at that moment. There were two sections of that class. The presentation was about to be conducted in a combined class of the two. Students from one section hardly knew at most two or three students from the other. Teasa and Cris were of the same category, they were from different sections. Students were keeping their topics secret.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day Teasa dreamed. In her dream, as far as she had remembered, she was lying on her bed and there was a big white piece of paper in front of her eyes. Some names were printed on that paper with some photographs. All of the photographs seemed to behave satirically. The photographs were like telling something to her. The words were pretty evanescent and after some moment they were out of her memory. It was her recapitulatory statement after waking up. The thing that she remembered was that she had seen Lizzie, from the other section, on that piece of paper. Then, beside the name “Lizzie” on that piece of paper, there was written something in bold. Then, she noticed the name of that very poet was written near the name “Lizzie” which she had suggested Cris for the assignment. And, she heard a voice too asking about that poet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next day, Teasa narrated her dream to Cris. They both laughed at it because Lizzie was a friend of Cris, but not Teasa’s and she hardly knew her. Then, they began to discuss the topic again. After collecting some basic contents for the topics, all students were to report the teacher the next day. One by one each one of them entered the class to put forward the topics. Lizzie came out and told that her topic had been rejected as the topic was too critical and huge, rather she was advised to take a part of the topic to discuss, only the poetic career. When Cris asked her the topic, he was surprised to get his own one in return. Now the teacher informed all of them that she would be evaluating further topics after the break. Cris was in trouble because a part of his topic had been already given to someone else. He was fraught with the gruesome hours he had to spend for a new topic. He was pretty conscious and not willing to talk to anybody. He had just forgot to remember the morbid connection of her prior cortical response with that dream.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the break, he met Teasa and told about what happened earlier that day. All on a sudden Teasa remembered her dream. Being a connoisseur of dreams, she started relating it to her dream. Cris came out of his weary thoughts and paid some attention to Teasa’s astonishment. They both were confused and started some discussion which lasted for a few minutes. Then, Cris went in the classroom after the break and the teacher surprisingly accepted his topic and told him to collect as much as he could about the history of that poet. Cris was too happy with the teacher’s response to his topic and he informed it to Teasa after school. Teasa was also happy with what happened and her topic had also been selected for the assignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That evening Teasa was thinking about the dream. What made the topic so exigent that Lizzie also came up with the same one. And, she hardly knew Lizzie. Why did she turn up in the dream? And, what could be the possible explanation for the unusual and morbid connection of her dream to the reality. Was it something to do with the frequent mentions of Lizzie from Cris? Or it was just the fear for the topic not getting accepted! It was pretty confusing and that very thought deranged her conscious state. She thought she could be able to thrive on the connection between her dream and the reality, but this was completely weird; not like the previous ones. The dream was too short, but was related to so many unconnected events in the reality. She figured out her reminiscences of her past activities and reckoned that the dream was an image of her fear and subconscious. Still it remained a mystery to her.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Teasa was getting ready for school. English teacher had given them an assignment, in which each one of them had to collect the history of a poet and present in front of the class. But, before the presentation, the teacher wanted to have a look at the names of the poets that each one of them was to submit to eliminate redundant names. Cris was pretty much confused about the assignment. So, he asked Teasa for suggesting him for a topic. Teasa was also trying to find one for herself. So, she suggested a name to Cris too. Cris was so confused that he asked about the possible sources from where he could get the information about that poet. Teasa helped him to some extent. And, they discussed the history of that poet for some days in school during the lunch break. There was a fear of redundancy among students. If one’s topic of assignment had been taken by any other, one of them had to sacrifice and take another topic. That could be tedious and arduous for one to change the topic for the assignment at that moment. There were two sections of that class. The presentation was about to be conducted in a combined class of the two. Students from one section hardly knew at most two or three students from the other. Teasa and Cris were of the same category, they were from different sections. Students were keeping their topics secret.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://thinktwor.github.io//loathsome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://thinktwor.github.io//loathsome/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Translucent</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Inner peace was all she wanted. Teasa dreamed a place full of light sources and she found herself partially weightless. Her clone in that dream (She used to refer herself as a clone while dreaming) was fraught with danger without any reason. The feeling was spontaneous. The excitement in her eyes was so mutilated that she couldn’t be able to figure out, what was the reason behind her bad reminiscences of her early days? In short, she was unsure of the reason behind her fear towards the future time or towards the light sources in her dream. She found her alone for sometime and as usual she heard very familiar voices and with each voice, she was witnessing a particular light going partially bright. After that, she found herself all alone in a street full of sky-scrapers and cars. People were moving here and there with full pace. She was witnessing a couple of known faces, who she had met before in her school. To her surprise, an old man came out of nowhere with a sneer in his face. He seemed neurotically obssessed with her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The face was not familiar, but that old man knew her before. He had a pale skin and a long beard and he was ugly. She didn’t remember, what that old man told her, while they met. All she remembered was that, she was in a house and it was pretty dark. The house was exactly like the house where she and her family used to live couple of years ago. The house was small with a wide entrance and a narrower room ahead of it. At the end of the room, there was a wide and comparatively large area, the passageway to the other rooms. To the left, there was the kitchen. She found herself somewhere between the passage way and the entrance. As she had been able to figure out the place as their old residence, she made her way to the entrance, though it was extremely dark. All of a sudden, she saw that same old man sitting at the entrance with his legs stretched out and he seemed to have a morbid fascination towards something. The scene was extremely scary and Teasa was at the verge of crying. She looked back to get some help, but all that she got was a “not so pellucid” view of her old residence. She was not able to scream as well. There was a small window right beside the main door and she was looking through it from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then she began to remember about that house. She remembered that uncle Ben was moving with his family into that same house that they had left. Her thinking about reality, led her to the question of her existence at that same place with no one in there. She again felt partially weightless and it seemed like she was going down steps and she woke up. It was a horrible dream with so many questions. Why did she find herself in that house suddenly after meeting that old man? Or the scene was so evanescent that she could hardly remember what happened along the way? A lot of questions were unanswered, but she never lost hope to find out a possible answer to all the questions she had in her mind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Inner peace was all she wanted. Teasa dreamed a place full of light sources and she found herself partially weightless. Her clone in that dream (She used to refer herself as a clone while dreaming) was fraught with danger without any reason. The feeling was spontaneous. The excitement in her eyes was so mutilated that she couldn’t be able to figure out, what was the reason behind her bad reminiscences of her early days? In short, she was unsure of the reason behind her fear towards the future time or towards the light sources in her dream. She found her alone for sometime and as usual she heard very familiar voices and with each voice, she was witnessing a particular light going partially bright. After that, she found herself all alone in a street full of sky-scrapers and cars. People were moving here and there with full pace. She was witnessing a couple of known faces, who she had met before in her school. To her surprise, an old man came out of nowhere with a sneer in his face. He seemed neurotically obssessed with her.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://thinktwor.github.io//translucent/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://thinktwor.github.io//translucent/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Solitude</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The ocean in Teasa’s next dream was pretty wondrous to behold, calm enough, moderately unstable and pale blue in colour. The horizon was loudly speaking to her in disguise and told her that the world was not round. Teasa was constantly observing the end of that ocean, but all she got was a view fading exponentially from her eyes. She was capable enough to put her legs into the waters, but she was unable to watch her legs getting wet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Countless efforts of watching farther resulted nothing but solitude. Once she had read about bees and their proximity of vision. But this was quite unexpected. The first view that she got, was the entire ocean with the proof of a flat world. Then, as time went on, the scene started fading away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She could hear familiar voices calling her name. The voices were random and the noise was unfamiliar. She sat down and tried to see her face in the water, but failed. The water was too cold and the colour turned light red. Then, she stood up and again the water turned blue. She was at the verge of speaking, but again she heard her name. She started walking back and the voices were getting louder and louder, and one particular yet familiar voice called her name pretty louder that she woke up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As usual, her mind was full of questions. Why the world seemed flat? What were the voices? Why the colour of the water turned light red? At last, she wrote the dream up to which she could remember and tried to relate and interpret the whole scenery with her pencil.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;The ocean in Teasa’s next dream was pretty wondrous to behold, calm enough, moderately unstable and pale blue in colour. The horizon was loudly speaking to her in disguise and told her that the world was not round. Teasa was constantly observing the end of that ocean, but all she got was a view fading exponentially from her eyes. She was capable enough to put her legs into the waters, but she was unable to watch her legs getting wet.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://thinktwor.github.io//solitude/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://thinktwor.github.io//solitude/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Extra Dimension</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Teasa dreamed again. This time very unusual and hard to explain. That morning she was reading an encyclopedia. Accidentally she went through the page of Pablo Picasso, the famous painter. She looked at a painting of some women. But she didn’t read the details of that one. She slept early that night and dreamed. In her dream, she was walking down a street and all of a sudden she happened to notice that a man with dark hair stopped near by with his bike. She stopped there. And, she saw something which was very much unusual. A woman came and sat on the back seat of that bike. Then, that man moved his head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teasa clearly observed that the woman was able to see the face and back of that man with the front view of that bike at the same time. Her eyes were red. It seemed like she was watching the man with great emotions. The concentration level of that woman was so intense that she was not able to hear anything else. Teasa was trying to tell something to them, but she failed and her voice couldn’t reach them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teasa woke up early and noted down what she had dreamed because she used to forget the exact content of her dreams. After school, she went through her notes and again a lot of questions were there in her mind. How can somebody watch the front and back of anyone completely simultaneously? Why that woman seemed to have no ears? Why her voice again faded away? After a long time, she concluded that the place where she was in her dream was governed by a completely different set of physical laws. She again opened her encyclopedia and went through that painting again. She read the details of that painting and she got shocked. Somehow she got her answers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Teasa dreamed again. This time very unusual and hard to explain. That morning she was reading an encyclopedia. Accidentally she went through the page of Pablo Picasso, the famous painter. She looked at a painting of some women. But she didn’t read the details of that one. She slept early that night and dreamed. In her dream, she was walking down a street and all of a sudden she happened to notice that a man with dark hair stopped near by with his bike. She stopped there. And, she saw something which was very much unusual. A woman came and sat on the back seat of that bike. Then, that man moved his head.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://thinktwor.github.io//the-extra-dimension/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://thinktwor.github.io//the-extra-dimension/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Shadow of Existence</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It all began when Teasa turned eighteen and her school final exams were about to start in a few days. Teasa was a kind of girl who used to take interest in some unusual and not-so-adorable topics. She was good at academics, but she never cared for subjects, which she didn’t find fascinating. That night she had with her some letters from her friends, chocolates and a glass of orange juice. She then closed the door of her room and she lay down on her bed, opened her physics book and went through optics. It was written that nothing can travel faster than light. Then, she began thinking of a vehicle moving at the speed of light and her attention was diverted and she looked at the newspaper, which was near her table lamp and all on a sudden she found a picture of a man with his blackish shadow. Close to her bed, there was her table. On the table, there was her table lamp and the bulb was glowing brighter. She took the newspaper and started thinking of sketching that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was three in the morning and she was in an about-to sleep state and while watching that picture, due to the effect of that glowing bulb, her eyes went down. The scene of the table lamp and the switch board (to which the wire of the lamp was connected) faded away from her eyes and she slept. All on a sudden she started dreaming. In her dream, she was walking down a street. Then, she saw a boy sitting on the road and crying hard. No one was there to listen. When she tried to call that boy, her voice faded away and he couldn’t hear a single thing. Then, she saw there was a building in front of the child. She couldn’t recognize the colour of the building at once. But she found that the building was made of some glass like material and there were pictures of some black birds on each glass piece. The interesting part was, the picture like structures of birds were moving here and there, but not coming out of the building.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And from the top of the building, there came a cone of yellowish light and the child started crying even harder. Then, the scene of the child and the building started fading away and the building after fading took the shape of her table lamp and the child went away a bit far and took the shape of one of the switches of that electric board. She opened her eyes with a lot of questions in her mind. It was six in the morning. I never asked her how much time the dream had lasted. But I heard that she used to tell that it had lasted for only four or five minutes. The questions were almost unanswerable. Why the birds were black and why they couldn’t come out of the building? Why couldn’t she recognize the colour of the building? Why the child was crying alone on that road? Why the building and the child took the shapes of things which were near her eyes? And, most important questions were - Why couldn’t she see her own face while dreaming? And, she started searching for answers and finally concluded that “Like in real life, we are not able to see our own faces while dreaming”. The second most important question was “What was real? Which she had seen while her eyes were closed or which she was watching with her eyes open?”. And, she thought that she was really present somewhere while dreaming.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;It all began when Teasa turned eighteen and her school final exams were about to start in a few days. Teasa was a kind of girl who used to take interest in some unusual and not-so-adorable topics. She was good at academics, but she never cared for subjects, which she didn’t find fascinating. That night she had with her some letters from her friends, chocolates and a glass of orange juice. She then closed the door of her room and she lay down on her bed, opened her physics book and went through optics. It was written that nothing can travel faster than light. Then, she began thinking of a vehicle moving at the speed of light and her attention was diverted and she looked at the newspaper, which was near her table lamp and all on a sudden she found a picture of a man with his blackish shadow. Close to her bed, there was her table. On the table, there was her table lamp and the bulb was glowing brighter. She took the newspaper and started thinking of sketching that.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://thinktwor.github.io//the-shadow-of-existence/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://thinktwor.github.io//the-shadow-of-existence/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
